{
    "1": {
        "1": [{
            "questionId": 1,
            "question": "DUNs Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "954574930",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 2,
            "question": "Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "CARGILL GHANA LIMITED",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 3,
            "question": "Site Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Tema Free Zones Enclave, Tema\nPMB 251 Community 1, Tema\nGhana",
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 4,
            "question": "Site Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": {
                "139": {
                    "customAnswer": null,
                    "optionValue": "Ghana",
                    "metadata": null
                }
            }
        }, {
            "questionId": 5,
            "question": "HQ Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 6,
            "question": "HQ Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 7,
            "question": "SIC",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 8,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": {
                "1081": {
                    "customAnswer": null,
                    "optionValue": "5149 - Other Grocery and Related Products Merchant Wholesalers",
                    "metadata": null
                }
            }
        }, {
            "questionId": 8,
            "question": "NAICS",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 9,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": {
                "1783": {
                    "customAnswer": null,
                    "optionValue": "311351 - Chocolate and Confectionery Manufacturing from Cacao Beans ",
                    "metadata": null
                }
            }
        }, {
            "questionId": 9,
            "question": "Business Classification",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 5,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": {
                "65": {
                    "customAnswer": null,
                    "optionValue": "Manufacturer",
                    "metadata": null
                }
            }
        }, {
            "questionId": 10,
            "question": "Ownership Type ",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 6,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": {
                "71": {
                    "customAnswer": null,
                    "optionValue": "Private company",
                    "metadata": null
                }
            }
        }, {
            "questionId": 11,
            "question": "Geographies Served ",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 3,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": {
                "50": {
                    "customAnswer": null,
                    "optionValue": "North America",
                    "metadata": null
                },
                "51": {
                    "customAnswer": null,
                    "optionValue": "Europe",
                    "metadata": null
                },
                "52": {
                    "customAnswer": null,
                    "optionValue": "Middle East and Africa",
                    "metadata": null
                },
                "53": {
                    "customAnswer": null,
                    "optionValue": "Latin America",
                    "metadata": null
                },
                "54": {
                    "customAnswer": null,
                    "optionValue": "Asia",
                    "metadata": null
                }
            }
        }, {
            "questionId": 12,
            "question": "Latest Annual Revenue",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Unknown",
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 14,
            "question": "Number of Employees",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "3654",
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 15,
            "question": "CEO Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Michiel Jehee",
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 16,
            "question": "Parent DUNS",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "954574930",
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 17,
            "question": "Website",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 18,
            "question": "Name of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 19,
            "question": "Email Address of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "EMAIL",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 20,
            "question": "Diversity Status",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 1,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 85,
            "question": "Global Ultimate DUNS Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 3,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "954574930",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 86,
            "question": "Global Ultimate Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 4,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "CARGILL GHANA LTD",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 87,
            "question": "Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 5,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "006249189",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 88,
            "question": "Extended Global Ultimate Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 6,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "CARGILL, INCORPORATED",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "2": [{
            "questionId": 21,
            "question": "Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 22,
            "question": "Contracting Party Loaction",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 23,
            "question": "Select the site function applicable",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 4,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 24,
            "question": "Describe the products / services you supply?",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 25,
            "question": "Which industries do you supply to?",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 2,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "3": [{
            "questionId": 26,
            "question": "Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 27,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 28,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 29,
            "question": "Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 30,
            "question": "Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 31,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 32,
            "question": "Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 33,
            "question": "Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 34,
            "question": "Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 35,
            "question": "Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "4": [{
            "questionId": 69,
            "question": "What is your total turnover?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 70,
            "question": "What are your total assets?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 71,
            "question": "What are your current assets?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 72,
            "question": "What are your fixed assets?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 73,
            "question": "What are your net sales?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 74,
            "question": "What are your net earnings?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "5": [{
            "questionId": 75,
            "question": "Is your company Privately Owned?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 76,
            "question": "Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 77,
            "question": "Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "6": [{
            "questionId": 78,
            "question": "The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 79,
            "question": "Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 80,
            "question": "The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 81,
            "question": "The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "7": [{
            "questionId": 82,
            "question": "Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 83,
            "question": "Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 84,
            "question": "Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }]
    },
    "2": {
        "1": [{
            "questionId": 1,
            "question": "DUNs Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "508619434",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 2,
            "question": "Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Recipharm AB (Publ)",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 3,
            "question": "Site Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Box 603",
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 4,
            "question": "Site Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 5,
            "question": "HQ Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 6,
            "question": "HQ Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 7,
            "question": "SIC",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 8,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 8,
            "question": "NAICS",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 9,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 9,
            "question": "Business Classification",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 5,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 10,
            "question": "Ownership Type ",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 6,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 11,
            "question": "Geographies Served ",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 3,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 12,
            "question": "Latest Annual Revenue",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 14,
            "question": "Number of Employees",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 15,
            "question": "CEO Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Bengt Thomas Eldered",
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 16,
            "question": "Parent DUNS",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "508619434",
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 17,
            "question": "Website",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 18,
            "question": "Name of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 19,
            "question": "Email Address of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "EMAIL",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 20,
            "question": "Diversity Status",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 1,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "2": [{
            "questionId": 21,
            "question": "Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 22,
            "question": "Contracting Party Loaction",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 23,
            "question": "Select the site function applicable",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 4,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 24,
            "question": "Describe the products / services you supply?",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 25,
            "question": "Which industries do you supply to?",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 2,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "3": [{
            "questionId": 26,
            "question": "Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 27,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 28,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 29,
            "question": "Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 30,
            "question": "Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 31,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 32,
            "question": "Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 33,
            "question": "Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 34,
            "question": "Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 35,
            "question": "Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }]
    },
    "3": {
        "1": [{
            "questionId": 1,
            "question": "DUNs Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "795448062",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 2,
            "question": "Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Berry Global Group, Inc.",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 3,
            "question": "Site Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 4,
            "question": "Site Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 5,
            "question": "HQ Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 6,
            "question": "HQ Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 7,
            "question": "SIC",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 8,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 8,
            "question": "NAICS",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 9,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": {
                "0": {
                    "customAnswer": "326199",
                    "optionValue": "DUMMY",
                    "metadata": null
                }
            }
        }, {
            "questionId": 9,
            "question": "Business Classification",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 5,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 10,
            "question": "Ownership Type ",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 6,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 11,
            "question": "Geographies Served ",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 3,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 12,
            "question": "Latest Annual Revenue",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 14,
            "question": "Number of Employees",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 15,
            "question": "CEO Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 16,
            "question": "Parent DUNS",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 17,
            "question": "Website",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 18,
            "question": "Name of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 19,
            "question": "Email Address of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "EMAIL",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 20,
            "question": "Diversity Status",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 1,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "2": [{
            "questionId": 21,
            "question": "Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 22,
            "question": "Contracting Party Loaction",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 23,
            "question": "Select the site function applicable",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 4,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 24,
            "question": "Describe the products / services you supply?",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 25,
            "question": "Which industries do you supply to?",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 2,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "3": [{
            "questionId": 26,
            "question": "Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 27,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 28,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 29,
            "question": "Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 30,
            "question": "Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 31,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 32,
            "question": "Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 33,
            "question": "Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 34,
            "question": "Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 35,
            "question": "Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }]
    },
    "4": {
        "1": [{
            "questionId": 1,
            "question": "DUNs Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "316067164",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 2,
            "question": "Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Siemens AG",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 3,
            "question": "Site Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 4,
            "question": "Site Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 5,
            "question": "HQ Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 6,
            "question": "HQ Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 7,
            "question": "SIC",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 8,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 8,
            "question": "NAICS",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 9,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 9,
            "question": "Business Classification",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 5,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 10,
            "question": "Ownership Type ",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 6,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 11,
            "question": "Geographies Served ",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 3,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 12,
            "question": "Latest Annual Revenue",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 14,
            "question": "Number of Employees",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 15,
            "question": "CEO Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 16,
            "question": "Parent DUNS",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 17,
            "question": "Website",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 18,
            "question": "Name of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 19,
            "question": "Email Address of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "EMAIL",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 20,
            "question": "Diversity Status",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 1,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "2": [{
            "questionId": 21,
            "question": "Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 22,
            "question": "Contracting Party Loaction",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 23,
            "question": "Select the site function applicable",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 4,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 24,
            "question": "Describe the products / services you supply?",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 25,
            "question": "Which industries do you supply to?",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 2,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "3": [{
            "questionId": 26,
            "question": "Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": {
                "1": {
                    "customAnswer": null,
                    "optionValue": "Yes",
                    "metadata": null
                }
            }
        }, {
            "questionId": 27,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": {
                "1": {
                    "customAnswer": null,
                    "optionValue": "Yes",
                    "metadata": null
                }
            }
        }, {
            "questionId": 28,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 29,
            "question": "Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 30,
            "question": "Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 31,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 32,
            "question": "Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 33,
            "question": "Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 34,
            "question": "Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 35,
            "question": "Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": {
                "1": {
                    "customAnswer": null,
                    "optionValue": "Yes",
                    "metadata": null
                }
            }
        }]

    },
    "5": {
        "1": [{
            "questionId": 1,
            "question": "DUNs Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "805619681",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 2,
            "question": "Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Aptargroup, Inc.",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 3,
            "question": "Site Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "475 W Terra Cotta Ave E",
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 4,
            "question": "Site Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 5,
            "question": "HQ Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 6,
            "question": "HQ Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 7,
            "question": "SIC",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 8,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 8,
            "question": "NAICS",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 9,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 9,
            "question": "Business Classification",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 5,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 10,
            "question": "Ownership Type ",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 6,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 11,
            "question": "Geographies Served ",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 3,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 12,
            "question": "Latest Annual Revenue",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 14,
            "question": "Number of Employees",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 15,
            "question": "CEO Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Stephan Tanda",
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 16,
            "question": "Parent DUNS",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "805619681",
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 17,
            "question": "Website",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 18,
            "question": "Name of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 19,
            "question": "Email Address of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "EMAIL",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 20,
            "question": "Diversity Status",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 1,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "2": [{
            "questionId": 21,
            "question": "Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 22,
            "question": "Contracting Party Loaction",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 23,
            "question": "Select the site function applicable",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 4,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 24,
            "question": "Describe the products / services you supply?",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 25,
            "question": "Which industries do you supply to?",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 2,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "3": [{
            "questionId": 26,
            "question": "Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 27,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 28,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 29,
            "question": "Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 30,
            "question": "Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 31,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 32,
            "question": "Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 33,
            "question": "Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 34,
            "question": "Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 35,
            "question": "Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }]
    },
    "6": {
        "1": [{
            "questionId": 1,
            "question": "DUNs Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "058321290",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 2,
            "question": "Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Clyde Machines, Inc.",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 3,
            "question": "Site Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "P.O. BOX 194",
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 4,
            "question": "Site Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 5,
            "question": "HQ Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 6,
            "question": "HQ Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 7,
            "question": "SIC",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 8,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 8,
            "question": "NAICS",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 9,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 9,
            "question": "Business Classification",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 5,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 10,
            "question": "Ownership Type ",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 6,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 11,
            "question": "Geographies Served ",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 3,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 12,
            "question": "Latest Annual Revenue",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 14,
            "question": "Number of Employees",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 15,
            "question": "CEO Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Edna Olson",
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 16,
            "question": "Parent DUNS",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "058321290",
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 17,
            "question": "Website",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 18,
            "question": "Name of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 19,
            "question": "Email Address of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "EMAIL",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 20,
            "question": "Diversity Status",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 1,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 85,
            "question": "Global Ultimate DUNS Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 3,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "058321290",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 86,
            "question": "Global Ultimate Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 4,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Clyde Machines, Inc.",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 87,
            "question": "Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 5,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "058321290",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 88,
            "question": "Extended Global Ultimate Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 6,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Clyde Machines, Inc.",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "2": [{
            "questionId": 21,
            "question": "Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 22,
            "question": "Contracting Party Loaction",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 23,
            "question": "Select the site function applicable",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 4,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 24,
            "question": "Describe the products / services you supply?",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 25,
            "question": "Which industries do you supply to?",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 2,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "3": [{
            "questionId": 26,
            "question": "Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 27,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 28,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 29,
            "question": "Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 30,
            "question": "Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 31,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 32,
            "question": "Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 33,
            "question": "Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 34,
            "question": "Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 35,
            "question": "Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "4": [{
            "questionId": 69,
            "question": "What is your total turnover?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 70,
            "question": "What are your total assets?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 71,
            "question": "What are your current assets?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 72,
            "question": "What are your fixed assets?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 73,
            "question": "What are your net sales?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 74,
            "question": "What are your net earnings?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "5": [{
            "questionId": 75,
            "question": "Is your company Privately Owned?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 76,
            "question": "Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 77,
            "question": "Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "6": [{
            "questionId": 78,
            "question": "The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 79,
            "question": "Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 80,
            "question": "The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 81,
            "question": "The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "7": [{
            "questionId": 82,
            "question": "Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 83,
            "question": "Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 84,
            "question": "Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }]

    },
    "7": {
        "1": [{
            "questionId": 1,
            "question": "DUNs Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "062503926",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 2,
            "question": "Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Esrp Advisory Dallas, LLC",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 3,
            "question": "Site Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "16000 Dallas Pkwy",
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 4,
            "question": "Site Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 5,
            "question": "HQ Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 6,
            "question": "HQ Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 7,
            "question": "SIC",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 8,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 8,
            "question": "NAICS",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 9,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 9,
            "question": "Business Classification",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 5,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 10,
            "question": "Ownership Type ",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 6,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 11,
            "question": "Geographies Served ",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 3,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 12,
            "question": "Latest Annual Revenue",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 14,
            "question": "Number of Employees",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 15,
            "question": "CEO Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Sharon Morrison",
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 16,
            "question": "Parent DUNS",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "062503926",
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 17,
            "question": "Website",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 18,
            "question": "Name of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 19,
            "question": "Email Address of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "EMAIL",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 20,
            "question": "Diversity Status",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 1,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 85,
            "question": "Global Ultimate DUNS Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 3,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "062503926",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 86,
            "question": "Global Ultimate Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 4,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Esrp Advisory Dallas, LLC",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 87,
            "question": "Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 5,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "062503926",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 88,
            "question": "Extended Global Ultimate Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 6,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Esrp Advisory Dallas, LLC",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "2": [{
            "questionId": 21,
            "question": "Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 22,
            "question": "Contracting Party Loaction",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 23,
            "question": "Select the site function applicable",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 4,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 24,
            "question": "Describe the products / services you supply?",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 25,
            "question": "Which industries do you supply to?",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 2,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "3": [{
            "questionId": 26,
            "question": "Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 27,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 28,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 29,
            "question": "Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 30,
            "question": "Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 31,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 32,
            "question": "Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 33,
            "question": "Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 34,
            "question": "Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 35,
            "question": "Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "4": [{
            "questionId": 69,
            "question": "What is your total turnover?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 70,
            "question": "What are your total assets?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 71,
            "question": "What are your current assets?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 72,
            "question": "What are your fixed assets?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 73,
            "question": "What are your net sales?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 74,
            "question": "What are your net earnings?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "5": [{
            "questionId": 75,
            "question": "Is your company Privately Owned?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 76,
            "question": "Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 77,
            "question": "Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "6": [{
            "questionId": 78,
            "question": "The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 79,
            "question": "Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 80,
            "question": "The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 81,
            "question": "The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "7": [{
            "questionId": 82,
            "question": "Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 83,
            "question": "Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 84,
            "question": "Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }]
    },
    "8":{
        "1":[{
            "questionId": 1,
            "question": "DUNs Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "176866937",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 2,
            "question": "Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Global Ground Support, LLC",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 3,
            "question": "Site Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "540 E Highway 56",
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 4,
            "question": "Site Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 5,
            "question": "HQ Address",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 6,
            "question": "HQ Country",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 7,
            "question": "SIC",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 8,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 8,
            "question": "NAICS",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 9,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 9,
            "question": "Business Classification",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 5,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 10,
            "question": "Ownership Type ",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 6,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 11,
            "question": "Geographies Served ",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 3,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 12,
            "question": "Latest Annual Revenue",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 6,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 14,
            "question": "Number of Employees",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 15,
            "question": "CEO Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "Air T Inc",
            "row": 7,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 16,
            "question": "Parent DUNS",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "024124661",
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 17,
            "question": "Website",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "",
            "row": 8,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 18,
            "question": "Name of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 19,
            "question": "Email Address of Sales Head",
            "answerType": "EMAIL",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 20,
            "question": "Diversity Status",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 1,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 9,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 85,
            "question": "Global Ultimate DUNS Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 3,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "024124661",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 86,
            "question": "Global Ultimate Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 4,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "T Air Inc",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 87,
            "question": "Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 5,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "024124661",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 88,
            "question": "Extended Global Ultimate Business Name",
            "answerType": "TEXT",
            "displayOrder": 6,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": null,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": "T Air Inc",
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "2": [{
            "questionId": 21,
            "question": "Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 22,
            "question": "Contracting Party Loaction",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 7,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 23,
            "question": "Select the site function applicable",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 4,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 24,
            "question": "Describe the products / services you supply?",
            "answerType": "TEXT_AREA",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 25,
            "question": "Which industries do you supply to?",
            "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 2,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "3": [{
            "questionId": 26,
            "question": "Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 27,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 28,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 29,
            "question": "Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 2,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 30,
            "question": "Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 31,
            "question": "Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 3,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 32,
            "question": "Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 33,
            "question": "Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 4,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 34,
            "question": "Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 35,
            "question": "Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": true,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 5,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "4": [{
            "questionId": 69,
            "question": "What is your total turnover?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 70,
            "question": "What are your total assets?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 71,
            "question": "What are your current assets?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 72,
            "question": "What are your fixed assets?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 73,
            "question": "What are your net sales?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 74,
            "question": "What are your net earnings?",
            "answerType": "NUMERIC",
            "displayOrder": 2,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 0,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "5": [{
            "questionId": 75,
            "question": "Is your company Privately Owned?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 76,
            "question": "Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 77,
            "question": "Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "6": [{
            "questionId": 78,
            "question": "The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 79,
            "question": "Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 80,
            "question": "The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 81,
            "question": "The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }],
        "7": [{
            "questionId": 82,
            "question": "Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 83,
            "question": "Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }, {
            "questionId": 84,
            "question": "Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?",
            "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT",
            "displayOrder": 1,
            "hasChild": false,
            "multiSelect": null,
            "optionMasterId": 10,
            "parentQuestionId": 0,
            "metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ",
            "answers": null,
            "row": 1,
            "selectedOptions": null
        }]
    },
    "9":{
        "1": [{ "questionId": 1, "question": "DUNs Number", "answerType": "TEXT", "displayOrder": 1, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": null, "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": "824623003", "row": 1, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 2, "question": "Business Name", "answerType": "TEXT", "displayOrder": 2, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": null, "metadata": "{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": "Harris & Ford, LLC", "row": 1, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 3, "question": "Site Address", "answerType": "TEXT_AREA", "displayOrder": 1, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": null, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": "9307 E 56th St", "row": 2, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 4, "question": "Site Country", "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT", "displayOrder": 2, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 7, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 2, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 5, "question": "HQ Address", "answerType": "TEXT_AREA", "displayOrder": 1, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": null, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": "", "row": 3, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 6, "question": "HQ Country", "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT", "displayOrder": 2, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 7, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 3, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 7, "question": "SIC", "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT", "displayOrder": 1, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 8, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 4, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 8, "question": "NAICS", "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT", "displayOrder": 2, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 9, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 4, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 9, "question": "Business Classification", "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT", "displayOrder": 1, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 5, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 5, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 10, "question": "Ownership Type ", "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT", "displayOrder": 2, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 6, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 5, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 11, "question": "Geographies Served ", "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT", "displayOrder": 1, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 3, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 6, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 12, "question": "Latest Annual Revenue", "answerType": "TEXT", "displayOrder": 2, "hasChild": true, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 6, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 14, "question": "Number of Employees", "answerType": "NUMERIC", "displayOrder": 1, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": null, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": "", "row": 7, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 15, "question": "CEO Name", "answerType": "TEXT", "displayOrder": 2, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": null, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": "Timothy M Harris", "row": 7, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 16, "question": "Parent DUNS", "answerType": "TEXT", "displayOrder": 1, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": null, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": "824623003", "row": 8, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 17, "question": "Website", "answerType": "TEXT", "displayOrder": 2, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": null, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": "", "row": 8, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 18, "question": "Name of Sales Head", "answerType": "TEXT", "displayOrder": 1, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 9, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 19, "question": "Email Address of Sales Head", "answerType": "EMAIL", "displayOrder": 2, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 9, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 20, "question": "Diversity Status", "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT", "displayOrder": 2, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 1, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 9, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 85, "question": "Global Ultimate DUNS Number", "answerType": "TEXT", "displayOrder": 3, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": null, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": "824623003", "row": 1, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 86, "question": "Global Ultimate Business Name", "answerType": "TEXT", "displayOrder": 4, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": null, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": "Harris & Ford, LLC", "row": 1, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 87, "question": "Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number", "answerType": "TEXT", "displayOrder": 5, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": null, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": "824623003", "row": 1, "selectedOptions": null }, { "questionId": 88, "question": "Extended Global Ultimate Business Name", "answerType": "TEXT", "displayOrder": 6, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": null, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": "Harris & Ford, LLC", "row": 1, "selectedOptions": null }],
        "2": [{ "questionId": 21, "question": "Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)", "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT", "displayOrder": 1, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 7, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 1, "selectedOptions": null}, { "questionId": 22, "question": "Contracting Party Loaction", "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT", "displayOrder": 2, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 7, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 1, "selectedOptions": null}, { "questionId": 23, "question": "Select the site function applicable", "answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT", "displayOrder": 1, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 4, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 2, "selectedOptions": null}, { "questionId": 24, "question": "Describe the products / services you supply?", "answerType": "TEXT_AREA", "displayOrder": 2, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 0, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 2, "selectedOptions": null}, { "questionId": 25, "question": "Which industries do you supply to?", "answerType": "MULTIPLE_SELECT", "displayOrder": 1, "hasChild": false, "multiSelect": null, "optionMasterId": 2, "parentQuestionId": 0, "metadata": "{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}", "answers": null, "row": 3, "selectedOptions": null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4": [{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5": [{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6": [{"questionId": 78,"question": "The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder": 1,"hasChild": false,"multiSelect": null,"optionMasterId": 10,"parentQuestionId": 0,"metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers": null,"row": 1,"selectedOptions": null }, {"questionId": 79,"question": "Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder": 1,"hasChild": false,"multiSelect": null,"optionMasterId": 10,"parentQuestionId": 0,"metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers": null,"row": 1,"selectedOptions": null }, {"questionId": 80,"question": "The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder": 1,"hasChild": false,"multiSelect": null,"optionMasterId": 10,"parentQuestionId": 0,"metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers": null,"row": 1,"selectedOptions": null }, {"questionId": 81,"question": "The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder": 1,"hasChild": false,"multiSelect": null,"optionMasterId": 10,"parentQuestionId": 0,"metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers": null,"row": 1,"selectedOptions": null }],
        "7": [{"questionId": 82,"question": "Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder": 1,"hasChild": false,"multiSelect": null,"optionMasterId": 10,"parentQuestionId": 0,"metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers": null,"row": 1,"selectedOptions": null}, {"questionId": 83,"question": "Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder": 1,"hasChild": false,"multiSelect": null,"optionMasterId": 10,"parentQuestionId": 0,"metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers": null,"row": 1,"selectedOptions": null}, {"questionId": 84,"question": "Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType": "SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder": 1,"hasChild": false,"multiSelect": null,"optionMasterId": 10,"parentQuestionId": 0,"metadata": "{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers": null,"row": 1,"selectedOptions": null}]},
    "10":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"064539372","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Interface, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"2859 Paces Ferry Rd SE # 2000","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Jay D Gould","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"064539372","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"064539372","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Interface, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"064539372","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Interface, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    },
    "11":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"031804839","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"John Bean Technologies Corporation","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"7300 Presidents Dr","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Chuck Durst","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"827055869","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"827055869","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"John Bean Technologies Corporation","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"827055869","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"John Bean Technologies Corporation","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    },
    "12":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    },
    "13":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"831776757","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Purecircle USA Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"915 Harger Rd Ste 250","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Magomet Malsagov","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"875671419","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"875671419","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"PureCircle Limited","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"875671419","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"PureCircle Limited","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    },
    "14":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"059769414","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Quality Sausage Company, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"1925 Lone Star Dr","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Gene Eisen","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"059769414","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"059769414","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Quality Sausage Company, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"059769414","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Quality Sausage Company, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    },
    "15":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    },
    "16":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"117949011","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Rousselot Dubuque Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"1231 S Rochester St","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Greg Schmidt","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"565562645","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"565562645","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"DII Holdings (Gibraltar) Limited","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"565562645","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"DII Holdings (Gibraltar) Limited","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    },
    "17":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"009181731","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Sage Parts Plus, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"30 Hub Dr Ste 1","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Mark Pollack","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"009181731","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"009181731","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Sage Parts Plus, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"009181731","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Sage Parts Plus, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    },
    "18":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    },
    "19":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"006160642","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Tony Downs Foods Co.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"54934 210th Ln","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Richard Downs","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"006160642","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"006160642","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Tony Downs Foods Co.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"006160642","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Tony Downs Foods Co.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    },
    "20":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"079713841","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Transperfect, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"3 Park Ave FL 39","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Elizabeth Elting","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"968273115","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"968273115","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Transperfect Global, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"968273115","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Transperfect Global, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    },
    "21":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"200356111","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Thompsons Limited","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"PO Box 250","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Dawn Betancourt","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"200356111","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"200356111","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Thompsons Limited","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"200356111","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Thompsons Limited","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    },
    "22":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"006958318","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Kelly Services, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"P.O. BOX 331179","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"George S Corona","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"006958318","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"https://www.kellyservices.com/","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"006958318","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Kelly Services, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"006958318","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Kelly Services, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    },
    "23":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"001408673","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Thermo Fisher Scientific Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"168 3rd Ave","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Marc N Casper","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"001408673","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"https://www.thermofisher.com","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"001408673","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Thermo Fisher Scientific Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"001408673","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"Thermo Fisher Scientific Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    },
    "24":{
        "1":[{"questionId":1,"question":"DUNs Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"DUNs number cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"006991681","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":2,"question":"Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"validation\":{\"errors\":[\"required\"],\"validators\":[true],\"messages\":{\"required\":\"Business name cannot be blank\"}},\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"United Parcel Service, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":3,"question":"Site Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"55 Glenlake Pkwy","row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":4,"question":"Site Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":5,"question":"HQ Address","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":6,"question":"HQ Country","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":7,"question":"SIC","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":8,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":8,"question":"NAICS","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":9,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":9,"question":"Business Classification","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":5,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":10,"question":"Ownership Type ","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":6,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":11,"question":"Geographies Served ","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":3,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":12,"question":"Latest Annual Revenue","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":6,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":14,"question":"Number of Employees","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":15,"question":"CEO Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"David P Abney","row":7,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":16,"question":"Parent DUNS","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"006991681","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":17,"question":"Website","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"https://www.ups.com/","row":8,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":18,"question":"Name of Sales Head","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":19,"question":"Email Address of Sales Head","answerType":"EMAIL","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":20,"question":"Diversity Status","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":1,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"custom\":[1],\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":9,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":85,"question":"Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":3,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"006991681","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":86,"question":"Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":4,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"United Parcel Service, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":87,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate DUNS Number","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":5,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"006991681","row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":88,"question":"Extended Global Ultimate Business Name","answerType":"TEXT","displayOrder":6,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":null,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":"United Parcel Service, Inc.","row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "2":[{"questionId":21,"question":"Site Location (Site that delivers the product or services)","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":22,"question":"Contracting Party Loaction","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":7,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":23,"question":"Select the site function applicable","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":4,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":24,"question":"Describe the products / services you supply?","answerType":"TEXT_AREA","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":25,"question":"Which industries do you supply to?","answerType":"MULTIPLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":2,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "3":[{"questionId":26,"question":"Do any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation hold or have held any position of employment with any government or government entity (including agencies as well as state-owned or controlled enterprises) or any Public International Organizations (e.g. World Bank, United Nations)?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":27,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any government officials or political party candidates/officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":28,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation political party officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":29,"question":"Does your organisation represent or act on behalf of your customer(s) either as an agent, consultant, or other third-party capacity to government, its agencies or regulatory officials?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":2,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":30,"question":"Has any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been employed by or performed services for one of your customers or any of its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":31,"question":"Are any owners (5%+ ownership), partners, directors, or key decision makers of your organisation related to any director or key decision maker of your customer (s) and/or its subsidiaries?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":3,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":32,"question":"Are you familiar with and do you understand your obligations under the U.S. Foreign Corrupt Practices Act or the UK Anti-Bribery Act?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":33,"question":"Has your organisation or any owner (5%+ ownership), partner, director, or key decision maker of your organisation ever been accused, subject to investigation, or convicted of bribery, fraud or any other corrupt activity (including offering or paying money or giving anything of value to a government official to retain business or obtain an improper advantage) anywhere in the world?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":4,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":34,"question":"Does your organisation appear on any country, regional or local or provincial government sanction or enforcement list in any country that your customer(s) operates in?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":35,"question":"Does your organisation have a gifts, hospitality and sponsorships policy?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":true,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"customAnswer\":\"Yes\",\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":5,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "4":[{"questionId":69,"question":"What is your total turnover?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":70,"question":"What are your total assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":71,"question":"What are your current assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":72,"question":"What are your fixed assets?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":73,"question":"What are your net sales?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":74,"question":"What are your net earnings?","answerType":"NUMERIC","displayOrder":2,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":0,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]}","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "5":[{"questionId":75,"question":"Is your company Privately Owned?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":76,"question":"Do you acknowledge and commit to comply with the requirements stipulated in the Nestlé Supplier Code?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":77,"question":"Are you the manufacturer of the goods to be delivered?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "6":[{"questionId":78,"question":"The company agrees to be audited by Nestlé or selected Nestlé representative.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":79,"question":"Do you agree to comply with the Nestlé Quality Requirements for Vendors attached and therefore are prepared to supply detailed information on your food safety and quality systems and processes?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":80,"question":"The company operates a certified food safety management system or has ISO certifications available for review","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":81,"question":"The company uses the HACCP-based approach or suitable equivalent for determination of food safety hazards and agrees to disclose this information to Nestlé.","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}],
        "7":[{"questionId":82,"question":"Are you prepared to supply detailed information on your systems and processes to ensure supply to Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":83,"question":"Do you have a business continuity plan / contingency plan that describes the measures your company takes to ensure continuity of Operations in case of unexpected events?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null},{"questionId":84,"question":"Do you have capacity to supply Nestlé?","answerType":"SINGLE_SELECT","displayOrder":1,"hasChild":false,"multiSelect":null,"optionMasterId":10,"parentQuestionId":0,"metadata":"{\"colsize\":\"col-lg-12\",\"boxes\":[{\"name\":\"label\",\"order\":1,\"style\":{}},{\"name\":\"input\",\"order\":2,\"style\":{},\"inputStyle\":{}},{\"name\":\"error\",\"order\":3,\"style\":{}}]} ","answers":null,"row":1,"selectedOptions":null}]
    }

    
    

}
